Maria's a teacher, but she's not smart enough to know that eating junk food's bad for your health.
That's all she ever eats. She's gonna make herself sick.
It's not like we're the poster children for health food.
Sorry, what was that?
As you know, you're fortunate enough to travel in the company of the Great Night Tribe.
If you keep spending your time hanging around an agent of the evil church,
I promise you it'll end in disaster.
Since my other half is already awake, I figured it was only right that I got out of bed as well.
Plus, I'm starving.
Good timing, then.
Hmm. Looks like you've put together quite the feast this morning, haven't you?
It's not all for breakfast, actually. Some of it's for lunch.
Well, well. Cooking multiple meals?
What have you done with my bro?
Well, have you finally recognized how awesome I am and decided to pay me the respect I'm clearly owed?
I already told you this yesterday.
That Maria girl doesn't eat real food. All she ever eats is junk.
So I thought I'd help out by making her a decent meal.
But don't worry. I made enough for you, too.
So Maria's the priority, and I'm stuck here playing second fiddle.
What'd you say?
What do you care?
Hey, where are you running off to?
Your food will get cold.
Cobito?
My brother's dumb. Big time.
Hey! Didn't expect to see you so early.
Not again. A person can't survive on potato chips alone.
Speak for yourself. These taste way better than any of the other stuff they have here.
Check it out!
Whoa. That's a lot of chips.
Yozura lets me stock up when I work for her.
You're like a pack rat. Guess I shouldn't be surprised.
Here.
Oh, wow. Did you make all this just for me?
That's very nice of you, but what's your angle, Kodika?
People don't just make food.
I don't have an angle, okay?
Just make sure you return my box.
I'll make your lunch for you tomorrow, too.
Wow. You're really being nice to me out of the goodness of your heart.
You must be some kind of saint.
I don't know what it is.
It's just that you sort of remind me of my sister when she was little.
I want to look out for you.
I didn't know you actually had a younger sister.
I guess it makes sense. You are the big brother type.
Yeah, well, I'd love to hang out, but I got to get to class.
Lay off the potato chips, all right?
Okay, big bro. You got it.
Big bro?
I've heard a lot of rumors about his dining habits.
Apparently, he always eats his lunch before lunchtime.
Please accept my apologies.
I'm so sorry my snack didn't satisfy your hunger.
That's not it, but thank you, though.
Big brother, hey!
Guess what?
I ate my lunch and it was so awesome.
Yozara's yucky potato chips taste like poo-poo compared to what you made.
Poop head Yozara likes to make people eat nasty poo-poo chips.
Oh.
Oh!
I was just kidding around. Your chips are the best.
It's weird to make a young girl call you big bro.
Do you have some kind of sexy little sister fetish or what?
No, and I'm not making her call me anything.
Kotika really is a big brother,
so I figured it would be the perfect name for him.
Gosh.
Wouldn't it be awesome to go inside a video game?
I mean, not really.
That was a joke. I didn't really mean that.
I just wanted to see the look on your face.
Don't be embarrassed.
Rika may not be able to get you into that game,
but there's one she can.
Rika has a different game you could play
where you might have a similar experience.
Are you serious?
How in the world do you have something like that?
After Rika helped them develop it,
they let her keep a copy of the prototype.
Want to try it out?
Yeah, of course.
So what? You put this on?
Yep.
It's the newest head mount display
from a game development company called Large Heart,
and it hasn't even been released.
But when it finally is,
these things are going to be huge.
Also included is the demo version
of this exclusive software.
It's basically the greatest
3D interactive fantasy video game ever created,
and it's called Romancing Saga 14.
Why Saga?
Because that's the prefecture they live in.
That's the reason?
Yeah.
It's pitch black.
I can't see a thing.
Be patient.
The software's still loading.
It won't be much longer now.
Saga, it is the final frontier.
Uh, that's not cool.
To bring an end to this world,
the reigning governor of Saga took action.
He summoned the Prince of Darkness
from another dimension
in order to destroy the Earth.
The opening is long,
so Rika will skip it.
Hey, don't do that.
I was really interested in the Valhalla Castle.
Sorry, too late.
First, you have to pick a profession,
and that'll determine the specific attributes
of your characters.
Valhalla Castle.
Right, so...
maybe I'll be this.
Oh!
Hey, over here!
Huh?
Oh, wow.
That's some outfit you got there.
Rika chose Gunner,
and this is what it gave her.
You don't look half bad yourself, Kotaka.
Wish I could see.
You can.
Just select equipment from the main menu,
and it'll show you what you look like.
What the hell is this?
I chose wizard.
Wizards don't dress like this.
Rika read about this urban legend
that says if you stay a virgin until you're 30,
you automatically become a wizard.
Rika thinks you look just about right.
Clearly, your character made it to 30 without doing it.
I don't want to be that kind of wizard.
Come on, this is ridiculous.
My guy doesn't even know any magic.
Rika would guess it is perhaps an honorary title.
Is this some sick practical joke?
Hey, what's up with your outfit?
Uh...
I wouldn't talk if I were you at all.
Huh?
Uh, wait just a second.
What the hell stupid outfit is this?
I chose blacksmith.
Now that you mention it,
it does sort of look like that.
Please, it does not.
I don't remember blacksmiths
dressing all bloody like this.
They can call forth swords using magic
and cut their enemies to pieces.
Actually, that sounds more like a ninja to Rika.
Oh, man, I screwed up.
I picked the worst possible job
with the worst possible outfit.
Would you quit your bitchy meat?
Uh, what are you?
I picked Rose Girl, and look what it did to me.
Looks like the developer got a little lazy
when he built that one.
But still, check out your attack prowess
and your magic ability.
They're through the roof.
Hmm.
As long as I'm still strong, I'm okay.
You really are in love with that costume, aren't you?
Hmm.
Not really.
Hey, you guys.
What do you think about my outfit?
Well, you, uh, you look very strong.
You're a very authentic-looking samurai.
Hold on a sec.
Senna, Yozara, and Yukimura
are obviously the muscle,
and Rika's the long-distance attacker.
What am I?
If Rika had to make an educated guess,
you're worthless.
That's not the answer I was hoping for.
I guess the only thing we're missing now is a healer.
Don't worry, guys.
I'm here.
Huh?
Maria?
You look exactly the same as you do in real life.
So I'm guessing you're the healer, then.
Yep.
I've seen that look before.
An acolyte of God is always an acolyte of God,
no matter what!
Since everybody is accounted for now,
should we get a move on?
Guys, check it out!
That's Valhalla Castle.
The Prince of Darkness lives here.
This mode is a simulation that ends
after you defeat the bad guy.
This Prince guy can be beaten in a simulation?
Remember what you're wearing?
This game kind of blows.
Looks like we've got company.
What are they, aliens?
They're completely disgusting.
They look and smell like poo.
I know them.
They're dragon gobies.
Hold on.
What the heck's a dragon goby?
Fish that inhabit the Ariake Sea and Kyushu.
I used to eat them when I lived there.
They don't seem very appetizing.
Of course, to each his own.
They're dragon goby soldiers,
the first of the small fry.
The only reason they're in the game
is because they look like aliens.
Man, that's terrible.
I don't care what they are or why they're here.
Let's kill them.
No, stop it.
Don't you feel sorry for them
being treated like monsters
because of how they look?
Dragon gobies may be weird looking,
but they didn't ask to be born that way.
Please, don't hurt them.
Just let them go.
You're a very good man
with a big heart of gold.
When you look at those fish,
you see yourself, don't you?
People as good as you,
they're hard to find.
Yeah, you're really the best, Kodaka.
Oh.
Thanks, guys.
Eat this!
Ah, poor little fish.
Why are you killing them?
What did they ever do to you do, huh?
Huh?
Come on, they're broke.
Rika knows how you feel,
but we can't move on till they're toast.
Their deaths will not be in vain.
They will live on inside each of us
as experience points.
Be gone, demon!
It's samurai mercy.
How come they aren't defending themselves?
They're working out a few kinks in the program.
Rika guesses the developer
forgot to code in the enemy attack patterns.
Oh.
Oh, poor little fishies.
The game was rigged.
I know they look super scary,
but really they're just delicious.
Huh?
That sound means we've made it to the next level.
Guess what?
My skills have increased.
And I can do magic now.
Did I get experience points
even though I didn't fight?
Everybody did.
Look, I got a skill.
Okay, it says,
don't be stupid.
Nothing will happen just from believing.
Nothing changes in reality
unless you take action
instead of just sitting around like an idiot.
Screw you.
And so,
we dispatched a variety
of dragon goby monsters
and finally arrived at Valhalla Castle.
Wow, it's so big.
The Prince of Darkness is a goby?
The developer really phoned it in this time.
Oh, come on.
No dialogue for the main bad guy either?
Bulletproof?
Senna, are you okay?
I didn't feel a thing.
The problem is I lost almost half of my battle points.
That's why we brought a healer with us.
Where is she?
Maria!
What's wrong?
Wait a minute.
Something isn't right about this.
Huh?
Yeah, Rika thinks she fell asleep on the couch.
That girl is completely useless.
I don't blame her.
The Prince of Darkness is pretty boring.
I think a nap sounds really nice.
You guys, if I use my rose guard, it will nullify the enemy's slashing attack, making it vulnerable
to a straight-on charge.
Well, what do you think, Senna?
Are you game?
Oh, I'm all over it.
Blasting hammer!
Here I come!
Do it now!
Yozara!
Hmm, these wall graphics look totally realistic, don't they?
Hey, what the?
That's gotta hurt.
She's dead.
Hey, don't get mad at me.
All I did was say I could nullify its attack in theory.
I never said I was actually going to go through with it.
You told her to charge it head-on.
Only because I knew she would be stupid enough to do it.
Thanks a lot, jerk!
Why the hell'd you do that?
Huh?
Hey, what is this?
Rose guard!
All right, way to go.
I hope it works before I run out of juice.
Yukimura, Rika, while I'm holding this thing off, circle around and launch a joint attack
from the rear.
Oh, right!
Okay, sounds good.
Rose guard!
What's wrong?
Hey, what the?
Ugh!
Yozra, are you okay?
Damn you, meat!
Damn you!
Victory is mine!
That's what you get for underestimating me.
I see.
She tickled her real body to distract her.
I wanted to die on the field of battle like a hero.
You're on your own now, Kodaka.
Don't leave me!
You guys!
Well, it looks like this is the end of the line.
Big bro!
Uh...
Maria!
Hey, when did you wake up?
Ugh!
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm okay.
Use your magic to...
Bastard!
How dare you!
Messing with my brother like that was a huge mistake, and I'm gonna make you pay for it,
buddy!
I may look innocent, but when you mess with my bro, the gloves come off!
Wait, heal me.
Hurry!
Hey!
I'm talking to you!
Ah!
That's it.
The...
End.
Uh...
Maria?
Kobito!
It's you!
This girl said she would save you if it's the last thing she did.
I figured I'd come check on you, and plus I've always wanted to know what keeps you out so late at night.
But I didn't expect it to be a video game for little kids.
Are you gonna introduce us to your friend or what?
How do you know this girl?
We're related.
Her name is Kobito and she's my little sister.
Come on!
There's no way your little sister could be this cute.
Hey, that's mean!
So what's going on?
Why did you decide to come here?
Well, big brother, I'm glad you asked that.
Lately you've been neglecting me and spending all your time hanging out with this bunch of idiotic mortals.
So I've come here because it's obvious you need supervision.
So basically you're upset because you feel your brother has put the club before your relationship,
so you wanted to drop by and check it out.
Is that about right?
No!
Not at all!
This girl has a brother complex, but I can't decide if I should hate her or not because she's just so darn adorable.
Please stop going on about how cute she is. It's creepy.
Listen, I'm sorry I've been coming home so late all the time. I know. How about from now on I make some pork bone ramen every Sunday to make it up to you?
Are you serious? You do that? Will you make it with extra garlic the way I like it?
Sure, why not?
Yay!
Plus, it's my day off so I'll be able to get some serious cooking done for once. I can also make you some lunch.
You're good at that.
Big bro!
Did you defeat the Prince of Darkness or what? I'm so glad you're safe.
What's gotten into you? Are you talking in your sleep?
I'm wide awake now. That game didn't last very long.
I'm so sorry, big brother. I wanted to protect you from danger, but I drifted off during the game.
Shut up! Dummy! Jerk face! Weirdo! You big stupid head!
Haven't you ever heard it's not nice to call people names like that, moron?
Shut up, you idiot! Who the heck do you think you are?
It's her. My sister, Kobito.
Wait a sec. This is really your little sis?
Would you please stop calling me that?
I am big.
I have not been little for years.
Well, is she your sister or not?
She's my sister.
He says you are.
I'm a member of the Night Tribe and have lived among humans for thousands of years.
My kind has been at war with you self-righteous church dogs for as long as I can remember.
They call us vampires and we strike terror into the hearts and minds of people everywhere.
A vampire! Yes, I'm familiar with your breed.
Tell me, what is a vampire doing here?
I've come here to keep my brother away from you so his mind isn't poisoned by a villainous member of the church.
On second thought, perhaps it wouldn't be a bad idea to join your little club.
You can't. You're still in middle school.
I don't know of any rule that prevents a middle school student from joining up with a club.
Yeah, since she's your little sister, it should be fine.
She's in. Plus, it seems pretty clear she has no friends.
What do you say? You want to join our club?
The only true friend I've ever had is the bitter darkness of the night.
You're right. She definitely doesn't have any friends.
Someone want to tell me why we're letting a vampire in? My vote's a definite no.
If you so much as touch a hair on his head, I swear.
He is an apostle of God who makes me delicious lunches, and if I so please, I'll touch every hair on his head.
Time for you to die. In the name of all that's holy, I render judgment on you.
Wrong, church lady. You're the one who will shrink before my dark magic. My darkness is so powerful, it once made a school classroom rip right in half.
How do you like this?
How about that? Your power is weak.
I'll show you weak. You're the dumbest person I've ever met.
Oh, boy.
I really do wish they'd cut it out already.
I mean it! I said let me go!
What do you think? Want to clean up?
Ugh.
You know what, guys? I don't think that game had a point.
What? If you had just watched out for me back there, that Prince of Darkness would have been dead by now.
Well, if you had been useful, we might have let you stick around.
What did you just say to me?
I'm saying you need to learn a little more skill with your...
They sound like your sister and Maria. Weird.
Yeah, they sure do.
I guess the lesson here is that we shouldn't let them play video games together.
That's too bad. Rika had a really great time.
It was the first time Rika ever played a game with other people.
That's the most fun she's ever had.
You really ought to go to a doctor and get that checked out.
Ha, ha, ha.
Oh, Yozora! Rika forgot to tell you your outfit earlier was so cute! Rika's totally crushing!
Hey! Don't tell me that! It's weird!
Rose Girl, she's super cute!
Stop! I promise you this, Jugs, I'll make you sorry you ever called me that!
I love you. My brother really is a good person.
You dirty vampire! Be gone now!
As a descendant of the Night Tribe,
I possess a power that is far greater than you could imagine, you church freak.
Is that right?
You are stupid!
I told you that won't work on me. Knock it off, kid.
Hey, I'm not a kid. I'm a full-fledged adult.
And I have a lot of adult knowledge about lots of adult things.
Yeah?
What sort of things?
Like sex.
Next, there aren't many customers at the karaoke box.
When you're under the covers with the man you love
and you count the cracks in the wall because you're bored,
that's all sex!
Be gone, apostle of God!
Let's do it again!
Go for it again,
we are done by theob stapes.
Go for it again!
To get it again!
When I'm upside down...
I might not know the Arstorn Blue then!
Go for it again!
Yep!
This time comes down the arstorn Hope.
ATRONY willing to recover the air 90 s.
yellow water這裡!
Whereas you die?
There are sometimes going on.
Here there are someети masamos and twoi cones.
Let's try and peep it again.
Let's bring on your attacker!